And the results of Harish ICICI have come, the
combined ratio has shown improvement on yearly and quarterly basis
and the way
this number has come around 101.2% and
104.5% quarter on quarter.  A
here the clarity in fact definitely
seems to be coming in on a strong scale with these numbers.  A 4.5% upmove
in the last session. Can the uptrend continue
?
If we look at the setup yesterday, it
is still a lower bottom setup.  I
feel that after this we may see an upmove out
which may see the stock
moving towards 1900 levels or even 1910.
So there is resistance around the 280 moving
average.  I think
fresh buying can be avoided.  But if
someone has already bought then
profit booking can also be done around this level.
Because I feel that it is possible that we may get to
see some tips
in the coming days.  So one should
wait a little for fresh buying.  Below tip: If it
comes around 1800 then one should
try to enter there once again.  If
anyone has a long position then I think you should
think about booking profits around 900.